import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet7: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "In landscape design, which of the following is considered an artificial feature?",
    "options": [
      "Natural Pond",
      "Brick walkway",
      "Grass lawn",
      "River"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a method of feature selection?",
    "options": [
      "Filter Methods",
      "Wrapper Methods",
      "Embedded Methods",
      "Interaction Features"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "Which type of reasoning deduces new information from logically related known information?",
    "options": [
      "Inductive Reasoning",
      "Abductive Reasoning",
      "Deductive Reasoning",
      "Common Sense Reasoning"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "Which type of reasoning is based on informal experiences and good judgment rather than exact logic?",
    "options": [
      "Deductive Reasoning",
      "Common Sense Reasoning",
      "Inductive Reasoning",
      "Abductive Reasoning"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "Which component is NOT a part of a Fuzzy Inference System (FIS)?",
    "options": [
      "Rule Base",
      "Inference Engine",
      "Fuzzification Interface",
      "Decision Tree"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "What is a fuzzy set?",
    "options": [
      "A set with a clearly defined boundary",
      "A set with no elements",
      "A set without a crisp, clearly defined boundary",
      "A set with only binary elements"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "Which AI framework offers an array of supervised and unsupervised algorithms and is based on Python, allowing the extraction of features from images and text?",
    "options": [
      "Jax",
      "Scikit-learn",
      "PaddlePaddle",
      "Theano"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "Which of the following AI frameworks was developed by Google's Brain team and first released in 2015?",
    "options": [
      "PyTorch",
      "Theano",
      "TensorFlow",
      "Microsoft CNTK"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "What is the main focus of Data Science?",
    "options": [
      "Past",
      "Present",
      "Future",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "Which process is generally used for the integration of data in Data Science applications?",
    "options": [
      "ETL (Extract-Transform-Load)",
      "ELT (Extract-Load-Transform)",
      "TLE (Transform-Load-Extract)",
      "LET (Load-Extract-Transform)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
